The entrance to the brothel is inside this door.
The actual establishment
extends out underground,
and according to the assassin,
there appears to be another entrance
in that building over there.
Then how about Climb and I attack there,
and you go in through here, Lord Sebas?
We can have him contain the entrance,
while I search through the inside.
Very well.
I have no objections, Lord Unglaus.
I wish you'd start calling me Brain.
Lord Sebas, I would be pleased
if you would call me that, too.
Mm-hmm.
All right, let's go.
--Right.
One other thing--
I will take as many prisoners as I can,
but if anyone offers resistance,
I will kill them without remorse.
You have no problem with that, yes?
Since our numbers are so few,
I think it is unavoidable to some extent.
But if anyone who might be
one of Eight Fingers' captains is here,
can I ask that you please apprehend them?
I am not a hardened killer.
It is not as though I am here
to kill everyone in sight, so rest easy.
Picking locks is not one of my specialties.
Wh-What the...?!
Hey, what was that sound?
It was rusted, so I had to
force it open just a bit.
There's a secret door right there.
Wow, that's a pretty handy item.
Yes. A certain lady gave me these
for such a time as this.
It is dangerous to go searching
around without a thief, after all.
Sure enough, it was booby-trapped.
A poison arrow.
So, what now? I'd like to have you
watch the entrance.
Would you wait here?
I'm not very good at indoor combat.
If possible, I'd rather keep to open areas,
where it's easier to fight.
Okay, you want to go together?
Yes.
Hey, what's the matter?
You through already? Eh?!
Now that I think about it, I liked
the voice of that woman who ran away.
Wha--?!
You like hitting, do you?
Y-You!
You hink you can ged away wi--
Sdob dat!
Is this wrong?
Ob course id is! Who do you hink I ab?!
A mere fool.
For pity's sake, isn't this an awful sight?
You hool--
Domebody! Id anybody dere?!
Why idn'd anybody cobing oud?
Because they are dead,
or they are unconscious.
Ib-b-boddible!
Now then, I feel no need to spare your life.
You are going to die here.
W-W-Waid! Why are you doing dis?!
You don't know,
even in light of all you've done?
I see.
I-I-I can gibe you boney, jusd don'd kill be!
This is what it means to be unworthy of life!
Stay there and die.
It's a bit noisy. Let's open it.
Do you want to wait here?
Yes.
Okay, I'm going to go look around inside
and be back right away.
Don't get yourself killed, Climb.
I appreciate it, Lord Ung--
Lord Brain, you be careful, too.
It's empty?
Oh, well, I guess.
And over here...
What are these? Spare uniforms?
And here we deliberately came
via the hidden passageway,
since the alarm alerted us to intruders.
Succulent, it doesn't do
any good mentioning that now.
Six Arms...
Oh, I know this boy.
He's the underling of that female
I hate more than anyone in the world!
You mean the princess?
I'd like to take the boy
back with us, too. What do you say?
I'll have to charge
a separate fee, if you please.
Okay.
Please help me!
Cocco Doll, it may prove a bit
difficult to take him back with us.
What do you mean?!
You're one of the Six Arms, right?
You're not worthy
of the name "Illusion Demon."
Illusion Demon?
I'll have to deal with this
before any reinforcements show up.
Nonetheless, I will try as best I can,
but please don't forget that
once you get clean away, we will prevail.
I'm going to guard this door with my life!
As long as nothing happens to me,
you guys aren't getting away!
We'll find out soon enough
whether that's possible.
--What?
--Sorry about that.
I'm going to kill the kid, right here.
You can't! He will make for
a fine card to play against that girl!
We've been fed the wrong impression.
If he had friends
on the other side of that door,
we would have been surrounded.
Then...
I am the only escort you have.
For us to get away safely...
...I have to kill him, right now!
Is that a Martial Art? A defensive battle
won't work here. Which means...
So that's it!
Hmm?
Your right arm itself is an illusion!
Your actual arm and sword
have been turned invisible!
That's right.
This is nothing more than magic
that makes part of me invisible
combined with magic that creates an illusion.
My character classes
are both illusionist and fencer.
It's not a very interesting trick
if you know how it's done, is it?
Feel free to laugh.
Seeing as how I divided my abilities,
I may be considered
lower than you as a warrior, per se.
However, are you able
to discriminate illusion from reality?
Multiple Vision.
Martial Art! Ability Boost!
Mental Enhancement!
Scintillating Scotoma.
Wrong one!
Martial Art! Evasion!
This one!
One out of two!
I guess... I can't say I've won yet.
But if I can apprehend Succulent...
Unfortunately for you,
that's not going to happen.
Fox Sleep. It's an illusion spell
that activates after being injured.
It hurt, too.
I'm afraid we're out of time,
so I'm going to finish the job now.
Listen, are you sure
we can't take him back with us?
Give me a break.
There's a good chance that this kid's pals
are on the other side of this door.
Please, let it go.
I can't... die yet... Not until...
I repay the debt... I owe Princess Renner...
I-Impossible!
That should have been a mortal wound!
How can you get back up?!
Why won't you die?!
Wh-What is this?!
Damn it, you use your feet, too?!
One last struggle, was it?
You sure gave me a scare.
Why don't you stop right there?
Right down to the wire, huh?
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and kill that guy!
If I tried that, he would rush me
and cut me down with a single strike.
Climb, are you all right?
Do you have any items that heal wounds?
Yes... I do...
Okay.
From here on, you're facing me.
I will exact retribution for him.
May I ask your name?
Brain Unglaus.
What? You're him?!
No way! It's really him?!
The old me might have felt pleased by the fact
that most of the people
I've met today already knew who I was,
but right now, it's a bit more complicated.
Hey, Unglaus,
why don't we call off the fighting?
You are a lot like we are.
Power... is what you desire, right?
I can see it in your eyes.
So why don't you join us?
Eight Fingers is the best organization
for those who possess power.
You can obtain powerful magic items!
High-value weapons and protective gear, too!
What tripe.
Is that all you people are?
What?!
I'm putting you on notice.
Our strength does not amount to much.
Also, there's one thing I've learned--
Strength on behalf of someone else
surpasses individual strength.
Maybe that's not much, but even so,
it's something I've realized.
What a shame, Unglaus.
Imagine, me having to kill a gifted warrior
who once fought evenly matched
against even Stronoff!
You think you--you, who wield your sword
only for yourself--can do that?
Yeah, I can kill you! I can kill you easily!
I'll kill you, then I'll kill
the kid slumped over, there!
Please be careful.
Succulent uses illusion techniques.
What you see is not necessarily real.
You don't say. That does indeed
make him a tricky opponent...
...but not a problem.
One strike.
What?!
I said I would end this
with one strike, Succulent.
Then go ahead and try!
My Field can detect even invisible beings.
You might have been planning to kill Climb,
then claim I couldn't protect him,
but you tried it with the wrong opponent.
See? One strike.
Nicely done!
Nicely done.
Wh-When did you get here?
Just this moment.
Y-You did?
I didn't detect him with my Field.
Who exactly is this man, anyway?
The women being held prisoner
have been taken into protective custody.
Thank you most sincerely!
I must remain here briefly,
for the after-incident report.
What about you two?
Oh, I think it's time I took off.
Then I shall take my leave, as well.
Welcome back, Lord Sebas.
Lord Sebas,
Lord Ains is waiting for you inside.
Is that you, Climb? Please come in.
Forgive me for being gone so long.
I was worried.
I really was worried, you know.
So, tell me exactly what happened.
I see.
Tomorrow, or the day
after tomorrow at the latest,
we will be staging attacks
on seven Eight Fingers facilities.
With the raid on the brothel today,
one can predict that as more time passes,
their security will grow tighter.
I'm terribly sorry.
This is all because I went off on my own.
No, please don't let it bother you.
We should think of it
as having made our resolve.
We arrested Succulent, one of the Six Arms,
as well as Cocco Doll,
head of their slave trade division.
This will be enough to shake
the very pillars of their organization.
Which is all the more reason why
I want to strike another blow to them.
Another blow, before they
leave the kingdom with any information.
As you wish!
I believe tomorrow will be a hectic day.
Please watch yourself.
Right!
Ho, Climb and that Six Arms man?
Yeah. He had been struck a fatal blow,
but it looked like he had
Succulent cornered pretty well.
Did he?
It's true, he has no talent with the sword.
So much so that when I first saw him,
I pegged him as nothing more
than a kid vainly struggling for power.
But then, he faced that terror--
the kind of bloodlust that rivaled
that monster I ran away from,
and withstood it.
In that regard, the boy is better than me.
How unbelievable is that?
Nope, the world is a big place.
The person that gave Climb
this training is one thing,
but this monster you say
you ran into has my attention.
Her name is Shalltear Bloodfallen.
I think she's most likely a vampire.
She stopped the technique I came up with,
the one I devised to defeat you,
with just one hand.
I see.
Stronoff, if you ever see her,
do not challenge her to battle.
I appreciate the warning. But if this
"Shallty" monster is after the king,
then I will fight her,
even at the cost of my own life.
That's "Shalltear." Shalltear Bloodfallen.
Hey, don't get any on the food.
It might take on the wine's flavor,
and taste pretty good.
My sense of taste is shot, so I wouldn't care.
Don't tell me yours is, too, Unglaus.
It's Brain.
Call me Brain.
Okay, in that case, I'm Gazef.
Got it, Gazef.
All right,
good night to you.
Good night.
Now then, the maid on duty tonight is...
Ah yes, it's her.
The one who looks like she's made fun of Climb.
Let's see, which face was the right one, again?
This is the smile I wear
when receiving others as a princess.
This one is best, isn't it?
You rang for me?
I have a request.
Can you prepare a bath for me?
Very good, Princess Renner.
Is something the matter?
It's amazing! Climb just performed
an incredible feat!
Then congratulations are in order.
You know what?
He put down these terribly bad men!
Then he freed some others
who had been held captive.
--They're at a guardhouse somewhere now.
--I'll kill her. I'll kill her, too.
--Is that right?
--If anyone makes fun of my Climb...
...I'll kill them.
I'll have to apologize to Cocco Doll, I guess.
Despite letting him have Succulent,
one of the Six Arms,
this place still fell as easily as it did.
So then, Boss, now that Succulent
has been caught, do we kill him?
The man does have his uses.
Reach out to the count and
ask to have him released within the day.
So what do we do? Step back?
I doubt that there's enough benefit involved
to justify the losses we'd take
in going up against this.
Don't be ridiculous. We have to make
an example of those who hit the brothel,
or our reputation will be diminished.
Don't even consider losses at this point.
Davernoch, the Undead King...
Peshurian, of the Spatial Slash...
Edström, of the Dancing Scimitar...
Malmvist, of the Thousand Kills...
As well as myself, Zero, the Battle Demon...
We'll show whoever attacked us a hell on earth!
We'll more than make them regret
doing anything this foolish!